Well, impressive as that may be,
Monte is not us.
(Sheldon:)Monte has no fear.
(Raj:)Sheldon, did we all
not just watch the same video?
(Raj:)Kripke's robot just had angry sex
with a mid-sized automobile.
(Sheldon:)You are overlooking the fact
we know what we're up against.
(Sheldon:)And we can modify Monte
so that he's prepared.
You wanna prepare him?
(Leonard:)Install a bladder and a pair of shorts
so he can wet himself.
How are we gonna make
any modifications without Wolowitz?
- Have you heard from Penny?
- Not yet.
(Sheldon:)Have faith, gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)We don't need Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)Engineering is merely
the slow younger brother of physics.
(Sheldon:)Watch and learn.
(Sheldon:)Do either of you know
how to open the toolbox?
(Howard:)And then when I was 14...
(Howard:)...I met Marcy Grossman.
(Howard:)She was so beautiful.
(Howard:)She just got her braces off...
(Howard:)...but they left a little of the overbite.